Guide to the Mario and Ruth Chamlee Collection
Stanford Archive of Recorded Sound
- Recordings
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 22, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 22, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 23, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 23, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 24, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 24, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 27, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 27, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 27, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 27, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 28, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 28, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 29, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 29, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 30, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 30, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 31, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 31, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 3, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 3, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 3, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 3, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 4, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 4, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 5, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 5, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 6, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 6, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 7, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 7, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 7, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 10, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 68)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 11, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 69)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 11, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 70)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 12, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 71)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 12, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 72)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 13, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 73)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 13, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 74)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 14, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 75)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 14, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 76)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 17, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 77)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 17, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 78)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 18, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 79)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 18, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 80)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 18, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 81)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 18, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 82)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 19, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 83)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 19, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 84)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 20, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 85)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 20, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 86)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 21, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 87)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 21, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 88)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 24, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 89)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 24, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 90)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 25, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 91)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 25, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 92)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 26, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 93)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 26, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 94)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 27, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 95)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 27, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 96)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 28, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 97)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)June 28, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 98)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 1, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 99)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 1, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 100)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 2, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 101)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 2, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 102)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 3, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 103)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 3, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 104)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 4, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 105)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 4, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 106)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 5, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 107)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 5, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 108)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 8, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 109)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 8, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 110)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 9, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 111)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 9, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 112)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 10, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 113)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 10, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 114)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 11, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 115)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 11, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 116)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 12, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 117)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 12, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 118)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 15, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 119)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 15, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 120)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 16, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 121)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 16, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 122)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 17, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 123)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 17, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 124)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 18, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 125)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 18, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 126)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 19, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 127)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 19, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 128)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 22, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 129)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 22, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 130)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 23, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 131)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 23, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 132)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 24, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 133)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 24, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 134)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 25, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 135)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 25, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 136)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 26, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 137)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 26, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 138)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 29, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 139)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 29, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 140)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 30, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 141)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 30, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 142)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 31, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 143)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)July 31, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 144)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)Aug.1, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 145)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)Aug.1, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 146)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Aug.1, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 147)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Aug.1, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 148)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Aug. 5, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 149)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Aug. 5, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 150)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Aug. 6, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 151)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Aug. 6, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 152)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Aug. 7, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 153)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Aug. 7, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 154)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Aug. 8, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 155)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Aug. 8, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 156)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Aug. 9, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 157)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Aug. 9, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 158)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Aug. 12, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 159)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Aug. 12, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 160)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Aug. 13, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 161)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Aug. 13, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 162)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Aug. 14, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 163)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Aug. 15, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 164)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Aug. 15, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 165)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Aug. 16, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 166)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Aug. 19, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 167)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Aug. 16, 1935 [sic], sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 168)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Aug. 19, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 168)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Aug. 19, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 169)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Aug. 20, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 170)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Aug. 20, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 171)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Aug. 22, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 172)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Aug. 22, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 173)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Aug. 23, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 174)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Aug. 23, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 175)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Aug. 25, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 176)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Aug. 26, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 177)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Aug. 27, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 178)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Aug. 27, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 179)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Aug. 28, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 180)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Aug. 28, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 181)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Aug. 29, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 182)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Aug. 29, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 183)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Aug. 30, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 184)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Aug. 30, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 185)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)Sept. 3, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 186)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)Sept. 3, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 187)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)Sept. 4, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 188)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)Sept. 4, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 189)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)Sept. 5, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 190)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)Sept. 5, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 191)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)Sept. 6, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 192)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)Sept. 6, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 193)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)Sept. 9, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 194)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)Sept. 9, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 195)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)Sept. 10, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 196)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)Sept. 10, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 197)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)Sept. 11, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 198)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)Sept. 11, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 199)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)Sept. 12, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 200)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)Sept. 12, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 201)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)Sept. 13, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 202)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)Sept. 13, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 203)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)Sept. 16, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 204)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)Sept. 16, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 205)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)Sept. 17, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 206)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)Sept. 17, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 207)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)Sept. 18, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 208)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)Sept. 18, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 209)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)Sept. 19, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 210)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)Sept. 19, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 211)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)Sept. 20, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 212)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)Sept. 20, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 213)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)Sept. 23, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 214)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)Sept. 23, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 215)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)Sept. 24, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 216)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)Sept. 24, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 217)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)Sept. 25, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 218)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)Sept. 25, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 219)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)Sept. 27, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 220)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)Sept. 27, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 221)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)Oct. 6, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 222)
  - Golden age of opera. Smetana, Bedrich, 1824-1884. Prodaná nevesta. Part I, 1 sound disc: 33 1/3 rpm, mono., 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 272)
    Performers:Pelletier, Wilfrid, 1896-1982, conductor; Burke, HIlda as Marie; Chamlee, Mario as Hans; Engelman, Wilfred as Kruschina; Browning, Lucille as Kathinka; Gurney, John as Micha; Rasely, George as Wenzel; D'Angelo, Louis as Kezal; Cordon, Norman as Springer; Bodanya, Natalie as Esmeralda; Burgstaller, Ludwig as Muff .Smetana, Bedrich, 1824-1884. Prodaná nevesta
  - Union Oil (Radio Program): Wandering Minstrel Nov. 9, 1939, 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 269)
  - German Refugee Benefit June 15, 1939., 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 277)
    Champion Recording Corp. WABC.Piccinella.
  - Shell chateau (Radio program; WEAF): Chamlee, Mario and Cordon, Norman, June 12, 1937, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 268)
    Universal Recording Company. (Duplicate)
  - Souvenirs of Opera and Song Dec. 6, 1965., 1 sound disc: 33 1/3 rpm, mono.; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 278)
    Test pressing. IRCC L-7029. Side 1: Performer: Fugre, Lucien, 1848-1935. Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Me«decin malgre« lui. Performers: Besanzoni, Gabriella, 1888-1962; Pauli, Piero, 1898-1967.Bizet, Georges, 1838-1875. Carmen. Prés des remparts de Séville.Performers: Chamlee,Mario; Bonelli, Richard. Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Forza del destino. Solenne in quest'ora Performer: Miller Chamlee, Ruth.Auber, D. F. E. (Daniel François Esprit), 1782-1871. Vielle chanson espagnole -- Hageman, Richard, 1882-1966. Miranda -- Massenet, Jules, 1842-1912. Thaïs. Baigne d'eau tes mains (with Harvey Harding) Side 2:Performers: Slezak, Leo, 1873-1946; Scheidl, Theodor, 1880-1959. Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Tannhäuser. Ich hörte Harfenschlag -- Loewe, Carl, 1796-1869. Tom der Reimer.Performer: Easton, Lorence.Schumann, Robert, 1810-1856. Myrthen. Nussbaum.
    Sonic Recording Products, Inc.
  - Mario Chamlee sings various songs and arias, 1 sound disc: 33 1/3 rpm, mono., 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 271)
    Side 1: Tosti, F. Paolo (Francesco Paolo), 1846-1916. Canzoni di Amaranta. Alba separa dalla luce l'ombra Alba separa dalla luce l'ombra -- Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Tosca. Recondita armonia -- Leoncavallo, Ruggiero, 1858-1919. Pagliacci. Vesti la giubba -- Siciliana -- Massenet, Jules, 1842-1912. Manon. En fermant les yeux je vois -- Meyerbeer, Giacomo, 1791-1864. Africaine. O paradis sorti de l'onde. Side 2: Thomas, Ambroise, 1811-1896. Mignon. De son coeur j'ai calmé -- Elegie -- De Ferrari, Serafino, 1824-1885. Pipelet. Questa notte mentre a letto -- Lehmann, Liza, 1862-1918. In a Persian garden. Ah, moon of my delight -- Out of the dusk to you -- Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Forza del destino (duet). Handwritten dedication: "To Maurice Happy Birthday. Mario"
    Audio Arts, Inc
  - Mario Chamlee sings Paquita., 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 279)
    Test pressing. Brunswick Master no. 13572. With annotation "Best Chamlee"
  - Open the Gates of the Temple., 1 sound disc: 78 rpm; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 280)
    Test pressing. Brunswick Sample Record Matrix 14842.
  - When my ships come home., 1 sound disc: 78 rpm; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 281)
    Test pressing. Brunswick Sample Record. Matrix 11618.
  - Various songs by Ruth Chamlee., 1 sound disc: 33 1/3 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 282)
    Side 1: Love's old sweet song -- The fulfillment -- Great peace -- Recompense -- Side 2: Veille Chanson Espagnole -- Debussy, Claude, 1862-1918. Chansons de Bilitis (Songs). Chevelure -- Fauré, Gabriel, 1845-1924. Clair de lune -- Hageman, Richard, 1882-1966. Miranda -- Oh, to be in England.